Are ya ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
I can't  hear  you.
我听不到你说话。
Kids:
Aye, aye, Captain.
孩子们：
是的，是的，船长。
♪ Ohh... ♪
♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
队长：♪ 吸水性的，黄色的
他是多孔的 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ If nautical nonsense
be somethin' you wish ♪
船长：♪ 如果是航海方面的废话
成为你所希望的那样 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
船长：♪ 然后降落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Ready? ♪
队长：♪ 准备好了吗？ ♪
All: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
全部： ♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ SpongeBob
SquarePants ♪
队长：♪ 海绵宝宝
方裤♪
: Ohh...
: 哦...
What the  ... Now?
什么……现在？
SpongeBob: ♪ La-la-la,
la, la-la-la ♪
海绵宝宝：♪ 啦啦啦，
啦啦啦啦♪
♪ La, la, la ♪
♪ 啦啦啦 ♪
Stop!
停止！
What could you possibly be
trying to do this time?
你可能是什么
这次想做什么？
I'm not  trying  to do anything.
我并不想做任何事。
I'm just having
a decent morning.
我只是有
一个体面的早晨。
By running around and
screaming like a banshee?
通过四处奔走和
像女妖一样尖叫？
Oh, Squidward, a banshee
screams like this:
哦，章鱼哥，女妖
像这样尖叫：
: Ahh...
: 啊...
There are two
kinds of people.
有两个
各种各样的人。
There are people
that are normal...
还有人
那是正常的...
and then there's you.
然后就是你了。
Really?
真的吗？
Yes, really!
是的，真的！
Maybe you should start acting
也许你应该开始演戏
a little more  normal!
正常一点！
: Dah!
： 哎呀！
I'm not normal?
我不正常吗？
: Ahh.
: 啊。
Squidward...
章鱼哥...
how does one become normal?
一个人如何变得正常？
Well, how about you start by...
好吧，你从...开始怎么样？
getting away from me,
you little creature!
远离我，
你这个小生物！
What's wrong with me?
我怎么了？
I need to understand  normal.
我需要理解正常。
SpongeBob: "How to Be Normal."
海绵宝宝：“如何变得正常。”
Hm, this videotape should help.
嗯，这个录像带应该有帮助。
Are you tired of
being called a freak?
你厌倦了吗
被称为怪胎？
Do people throw you
out of their homes?
人们会扔你吗
离开他们的家？
Well, do they?
嗯，是吗？
Yes, yes and yes.
是的，是的，是的。
Then join me as I take you on
然后加入我，我带你去
a "Journey Into Normality."
“回归常态之旅”。
Normality.
常态。
The life of a normal person
is relatively simple.
一个正常人的生活
比较简单。
Here is your typical average Joe
on his way to work.
这是典型的普通乔
在上班的路上。
See how he is dressed.
看看他穿得怎么样。
Even his hair is boring.
甚至他的头发也很无聊。
Notice his features,
nice and smooth
注意他的特点，
漂亮又光滑
without a crater
or freckle to be seen.
没有火山口
或可见雀斑。
Crater and freckles?
火山口和雀斑？
In his office space
在他的办公空间里
Mr. Normal, at least
至少正常先生
that's what it says
on his name tag
就是这么说的
在他的名字标签上
works at a steady
and monotonous pace
工作稳定
和单调的节奏
just as all
the other normals do.
正如所有人一样
其他法线也是如此。
Take note of
how they communicate
with each other.
请注意
他们如何沟通
与彼此。
Hi, how
are you?
你好你好吗？
at the end of the day
归根结底
Mr. Normal packs his things
正常先生收拾东西
and goes home to merrily start
the cycle again in the morning.
回家愉快地开始
早上再次循环。
Yeah...
是的...
I want one
Krabby Patty.
我想要一个
克拉比·帕蒂。
SpongeBob, I need
one Krabby Patty.
海绵宝宝，我需要
一份蟹肉饼。
what, no annoying blurbs today?
什么，今天没有烦人的简介吗？
Hmm, strangely quiet.
嗯，出奇的安静。
SpongeBob?
海绵宝宝？
Hi, how are you?
你好你好吗？
What's the meaning of this?
这有什么意义呢？
I took your advice.
我采纳了你的建议。
From now on, I'm normal.
从现在开始，我就是正常人了。
Normal, huh?
正常吧？
Yup.
是的。
Oh, really?
哦真的吗？
Yup.
是的。
Whatever.
任何。
I know you're just waiting
to say something stupid.
我知道你只是在等待
说一些愚蠢的话。
Wonderful weather
we're having.
天气真好
我们有。
Uh, yes, it is.
呃，是的，是的。
Ok, see you around.
好的，再见。
Yeah, I'll, uh...
是的，我会，呃...
I'll see you.
我会见到你。
SpongeBob, what are you
doing sitting around?
海绵宝宝，你是什么
闲坐做什么？
We need Krabby Patties
out there.
我们需要蟹肉饼
在那里。
Yes, sir.
是的，先生。
I'll do it normally.
我会正常做。
Hey?
嘿？
wow, that's all it takes
these days, huh?
哇，这就是所需要的
这几天吧？
Can you do more?
你能做更多吗？
Oh, my!
哦，天哪！
It's like printing money.
这就像印钱一样。
I wonder what
got into SpongeBob.
我想知道什么
进入了海绵宝宝。
And what the heck is that?
那到底是什么？
Squidward: Whose
house is this?
章鱼哥：谁的
房子是这个吗？
Hi, how are you?
你好你好吗？
Hi, SpongeBob.
嗨，海绵宝宝。
Hi, how are you?
你好你好吗？
Good, just coming by to
很好，刚好过来
get a drink.
喝一杯。
Wonderful weather
we're having.
天气真好
我们有。
It sure is.
确实如此。
Ok, see you 'round.
好的，再见。
Yeah...  .
是的...  。
See you  .
再见  。
Oh, my  .
哦，我的。
I could get used to this.
我可以习惯这个。
French man: Three weeks later.
法国人：三周后。
There you are, sir.
就在这儿，先生。
Oh, yes, it's time
again  .
哦，是的，是时候了
再次。
I've been meaning
to say this but
我一直想说
这么说但是
I've come to appreciate
your demeanor lately.
我已经开始欣赏
你最近的神态。
You know, it's
a funny thing, Squidward.
你知道，这是
有趣的是，章鱼哥。
I smoothed out the edges
of my personality
我平滑了边缘
我的个性
and the rest just
followed suit.
剩下的只是
也纷纷效仿。
Now I am utterly normal.
现在我完全正常了。
Ugh, that ain't right.
呃，那是不对的。
I will never spend
money here again.
我永远不会花费
钱又来了。
Never?
绝不？
Come on, guys.
来吧，伙计们。
These patties ain't worth
the paper they're printed on.
这些肉饼不值钱
打印它们的纸张。
Wait, where you going?
等等，你要去哪里？
Krabs: SpongeBob!
蟹蟹：海绵宝宝！
What are you doing back here?
你回来做什么？
Do you expect the customers
to eat this?
你期望顾客
吃这个？
And now, thanks to you,
they're leaving in boat loads.
现在，多亏了你，
他们正满载船只离开。
Maybe this thing is out of ink.
也许这东西没墨水了。
No, boy, you're
missing the point.
不，孩子，你是
没有抓住要点。
You can't make Krabby Patties
with ink and paper.
你不能做蟹黄馅饼
用墨水和纸。
You gotta put your
heart into it, boy.
你必须把你的
心投入其中，男孩。
Now get back to making them
patties the right way
现在回去制作它们
肉饼的正确做法
and stop acting so dull.
别再表现得那么迟钝了。
What you call dull
I call normal.
你所谓的沉闷
我称正常。
Well, till you decide to
start making them patties
好吧，直到你决定
开始给他们做肉饼
the way only you can
只有你能做到的方式
I want you out of my place.
我要你离开我的位置。
I guess the decision
to be normal
我猜这个决定
正常
was more life changing
than I thought.
改变了更多的生活
比我想象的要多。
Hi, how are you?
你好你好吗？
What happened to you?
你怎么了？
Oh, I got normal.
哦，我恢复正常了。
Whatever that means.
不管那意味着什么。
Hey, SpongeBob, what do you say
嘿，海绵宝宝，你说什么
we charge into jellyfish fields
我们冲进水母区
nets a-blaze?
网着火了？
Let's do something normal
like window shopping.
我们来做点正常的事吧
就像逛街一样。
Let's do this.
让我们这样做吧。
Ah!
啊!
Yeah-ha,
hey, your turn.
是啊哈，
嘿，轮到你了。
I think I'll pass.
我想我会通过的。
But I do need to
defragment my hard drive.
但我确实需要
对我的硬盘进行碎片整理。
Would you like to help?
您愿意帮忙吗？
Hey, listen...
嘿，听着……
when you decide
to do something fun
当你决定时
做一些有趣的事情
you know where
to find me.
你知道在哪里
来找我。
Ok, see you around.
好的，再见。
Hi, how are you?
你好你好吗？
I never thought I'd
hear myself say this but
我从没想过我会
听到我自己这么说但是
please come in, SpongeBob.
请进来，海绵宝宝。
Thank you.
谢谢。
Tell me, what are you doing
cooped up in here
告诉我，你在做什么
关在这儿
when the weather outside
is so normal?
当外面的天气
有那么正常吗？
Well, today is dusting day.
嗯，今天是除尘日。
The day I dust
my 483 self-portraits.
我除尘的那一天
我的 483 张自画像。
Wow, that's something you
don't see in the average house.
哇，那是你的东西
一般房子里看不到。
You know, SpongeBob, it's ok
to be a little different.
你知道，海绵宝宝，没关系
有点不同。
And you know what
else is abnormal?
你知道吗
不然不正常吗？
Your nose- it's all
bulbous and flappy.
你的鼻子——这就是一切
球状且蓬松。
Your eyes are
a little odd, too.
你的眼睛是
也有点奇怪。
Looks like your whole face
could use some work.
看起来像你的整张脸
可以使用一些工作。
Mm, yeah, there we go.
嗯，是的，我们开始了。
See?
看？
Looking normal already.
看起来已经很正常了
What the...
什么...
You don't wear pants.
你没穿裤子。
And stay out of my home.
并且别来我家。
Oh, what happened?
噢，发生什么事了？
I lost my job and my best friend
我失去了工作和最好的朋友
and now I'm too normal
for Squidward.
现在我太正常了
为了章鱼哥。
Maybe I have taken this
normal thing too far.
也许我已经采取了这个
正常的事情太远了。
No problem, SpongeBob.
没问题，海绵宝宝。
You made yourself normal.
你让自己变得正常了。
Now all you have to do
is reweird yourself.
现在你所要做的就是
是你自己很奇怪。
All it'll take
is a mental adjustment
and some tight clenching.
一切都将需要
是一种心理调整
和一些紧握。
Now focus...
现在重点...
: And  clench.
: 并握紧。
Oh, well...
那好吧...
If I'm going to get weird
如果我会变得奇怪
I'm going to need
to see a professional.
我需要
去看专业人士。
: Look at my tongue.
: 看看我的舌头。
That's very nice, Patrick
非常好，帕特里克
but I need you to retrain me.
但我需要你重新训练我。
I want to be abnormal again.
我想再次变得不正常。
Huh, I don't think you
have what it takes.
呵呵，我不认为你
拥有所需的一切。
Please, Patrick.
拜托，帕特里克。
If anyone can teach me
the arcane art of
the weird, it's you.
如果有人可以教我
的神秘艺术
最奇怪的是你。
Teach me to how
to be me, again.
教我如何
再次成为我。
It won't be easy
这并不容易
but I'll do it.
但我会做的。
Oh, thank you, Patrick.
哦，谢谢你，帕特里克。
But first, I'll need a garden
hose and a flatbed truck
但首先我需要一个花园
软管和平板卡车
and I'll need you
to remove your trousers.
我需要你
脱掉你的裤子。
Patrick, I'm feeling very
self-conscious right now.
帕特里克，我感觉很
现在有自我意识。
Try to concentrate on your
first lesson in weird.
尝试集中精力于你的
奇怪的第一课。
See you on the
other side, buddy.
见
另一边，伙计。
Patrick: Oh, ho-ho...
帕特里克：噢，嗬嗬……
Patrick: Whoo-hoo.
帕特里克：呼呼。
Mommy, Mommy...
妈妈，妈妈……
what are those things?
那些东西是什么？
Those are
undesirables, honey.
那些是
不受欢迎的，亲爱的。
We only talk
to normal people.
我们只说话
对正常人来说。
SpongeBob, the weird
therapy is working.
海绵宝宝，奇怪的
治疗正在发挥作用。
Your craters
are coming back.
你的陨石坑
正在回来。
We just have to keep
pushing the boundaries.
我们只需要保持
突破界限。
We've gotta get stranger.
我们必须变得陌生了。
Talk backwards.
倒着说。
"Chap Beru suoy era?"
“Chap Beru suoy时代？”
Mmm...
嗯...
What's happening?
发生什么事了？
The final transformation.
最后的转变。
Huh?
啊？
What happened?
发生了什么？
I don't know.
我不知道。
I guess I became
permanently normal.
我想我变成了
永久正常。
No!
不！
: I don't
wanna be normal.
: 我不
想要正常。
Go away.
离开。
Normal is not
worth it.
正常的不是
值得的。
It's me, Squidward.
是我，章鱼哥。
I'm looking
for SpongeBob.
我在找
对于海绵宝宝。
Hi.
你好。
How are you?
你好吗？
SpongeBob, you're back
to your square shape.
海绵宝宝你回来了
到你的正方形。
Wow, I guess
Squidward's normal looks
哇，我猜
章鱼哥的正常外貌
scared me back
to my original form.
吓我回来
到我原来的形式。
Thank, buddy,
you saved my life.
谢谢，哥们，
你救了我的命。
Wonderful weather
we're having, hm?
天气真好
我们有，嗯？
It sure is, buddy.
确实如此，伙计。
It sure is.
确实如此。
Ooh...
哦...
... Whoa.
... 哇。
Gary, come and get it.
加里，过来拿它。
Gary...
加里...
Gary?
加里？
Gary.
加里.
Gary?
加里？
Gary!
加里！
Huh? Gary must've gotten
an early start.
啊？加里一定已经得到了
早点开始。
Rise and shine, Squidward.
崛起并闪耀，章鱼哥。
You don't wanna be late again.
你不想再迟到了。
Ok, see you at the Krusty Krab.
好的，我们蟹堡王见。
Guess Squidward needs
his beauty sleep.
猜猜章鱼哥需要什么
他的美容觉。
Not everyone is blessed
with my natural good looks.
不是每个人都被祝福
以我天生的美貌。
Patrick, it's morning.
帕特里克，早上了。
You don't wanna
forget to wake up again.
你不想
忘记再次醒来。
Patrick?
帕特里克？
Ok, see you after
work, sleepyhead.
好的，稍后见
工作，瞌睡虫。
♪ La-la-la, la, la-la-la ♪
♪ 啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦 ♪
Hm, slow day.
嗯，缓慢的一天。
Good night, Squidward.
晚安，章鱼哥。
Good night, Mr. Krabs.
晚安，蟹老板。
Gary, I'm home.
加里，我回来了。
Gary, you here, buddy?
加里，你在吗，伙计？
Gary?
加里？
He hasn't touched his food.
他没有碰过他的食物。
: Squidward!
: 乌贼王！
Open up!
打开！
Squidward, have you seen Gary?
章鱼哥，你看到加里了吗？
He's gone missing.
他失踪了。
Squidward?
章鱼哥？
Not a sign
of Squidward anywhere.
不是一个迹象
章鱼哥在任何地方。
Squidward?
章鱼哥？
You up here?
你在上面吗？
Hm, Squidward's clarinet.
嗯，章鱼哥的单簧管。
Um, um, um...
嗯，嗯，嗯……
It's not even warm.
甚至都不热。
Squidward's missing, too.
章鱼哥也失踪了。
Patrick! Open up.
帕特里克！打开。
Squidward and Gary are missing.
章鱼哥和加里失踪了。
Patrick's gone too.
帕特里克也走了。
What if everybody's gone?
如果大家都走了怎么办？
SpongeBob: Mr. Krabs!
海绵宝宝：蟹老板！
He's gone, too.
他也走了。
Sandy... She's gone.
桑迪……她走了。
Gone.
走了。
Gone!
走了！
Where did everybody go...
大家都去哪儿了...
: go...
： 去...
go...
去...
...go?
...去？
Everybody's gone.
大家都走了。
But I swear that
I will keep the memory
但我发誓
我会保留记忆
of Bikini Bottom alive
比基尼泳裤还活着
by living out their
lives for them.
通过活出他们的
为他们而活。
:
SpongeBob...
：
海绵宝宝...
Would you be quiet?
你能安静点吗？
You're disrupting my genius.
你正在破坏我的天才。
Mr. Krabs, sir,
can I have a raise?
蟹老板先生，先生，
我可以加薪吗？
No, now get to work.
不，现在开始工作。
Yes, sir, Mr. Krabs, sir.
是的，先生，蟹老板先生，先生。
:
Excuse me, sonny.
：
对不起，儿子。
May I have a Krabby Patty
deluxe, please?
我可以吃一个蟹肉饼吗
请问豪华版可以吗？
SpongeBob: Right away,
sir, I mean...
海绵宝宝：马上，
先生，我的意思是...
:
I mean, ahem, whatever.
：
我的意思是，咳咳，无论如何。
Hey, SpongeBob, we've got an
order for a Krabby Patty deluxe.
嘿，海绵宝宝，我们有一个
订购一份豪华蟹肉饼。
Heaven knows why  .
天知道为什么。
SpongeBob: Coming up, Squidward.
海绵宝宝：来了，章鱼哥。
SpongeBob: Excuse me, Sandy.
海绵宝宝：对不起，桑迪。
But may I have some more of
this delicious ice tea?
但我可以再多一些吗
这美味的冰茶？
:
Why sure.
：
为什么肯定。
Oop, just a sec.
哎呀，等一下。
Ah! Ooh.
啊!哦。
Why sho' 'nuff, SpongeBob.
为什么要生气呢，海绵宝宝。
:
Good morning, class.
：
早上好，同学们。
Can anyone tell me
the first thing you do
谁能告诉我
你做的第一件事
when driving a boat?
驾驶船时？
Ah, um, floor it?
啊，嗯，地板吗？
That's right, you floor it.
没错，你把它铺平了。
Excellent work, SpongeBob.
干得好，海绵宝宝。
Why, thank you Mrs.
何必呢，谢谢小姐姐
Pu... Puff  .
噗……噗。
This is pointless.
这是毫无意义的。
I know, Mrs. Puff.
我知道，帕夫夫人。
: I can't
replace everyone.
: 我不能
替换所有人。
I'll never be happy again.
我永远不会再快乐了。
Ooh, blank driver's license.
哦，空白驾照。
That's the baby.
那就是婴儿。
Hi, fella, it's me.
嗨，伙计，是我。
it's ok, I'm licensed.
没关系，我有授权。
♪ La, la-la-la, la, la, la ♪
♪ 啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦 ♪
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
Listen to that purr.
听那咕噜声。
♪ La, la, la-la-la... ♪
♪ 啦，啦，啦啦啦……♪
♪ La, la, la... ♪
♪ 啦，啦，啦……♪
♪ La, la-la-la, la ♪
♪ 啦，啦啦啦，啦 ♪
♪ La, la, la-la ♪
♪ 啦啦啦啦 ♪
♪ La-la, la-la... ♪
♪ 啦啦，啦啦……♪
♪ La-la-la-la, la, la... ♪
♪ 啦啦啦啦，啦啦啦……♪
Mmm, good night, Boatie.
嗯，晚安，博蒂。
SpongeBob: Uh, uh, uh, wha...
海绵宝宝：呃呃呃呃呃……
Ah, ah!
啊啊啊！
Ah, ha, no, no...
啊哈，不，不……
No!
不！
Oh, Gary,
I had a nightmare
哦，加里，
我做了一个噩梦
that all my friends were gone
我所有的朋友都走了
and I was
driving a...  .
我当时
驾驶着...
So it was true.
所以这是真的。
I guess it's just
you and me now, Boatie.
我想这只是
现在你和我，博蒂。
This is where I work.
这是我工作的地方。
Wanna help me cook up
some Krabby Patties?
想帮我做饭
一些蟹黄馅饼？
Great.
伟大的。
Back when everyone was around
they used to really enjoy these.
当大家都在身边的时候
他们曾经非常喜欢这些。
Here, try one.
来，尝试一下。
What? You don't
like Krabby Patties?
什么？你不
像蟹黄饼一样？
Huh.
呵呵。
Well, I guess we can
still make this work.
好吧，我想我们可以
仍然使这项工作有效。
Oh, boy...
哦，男孩……
We learned a lot
about each other today.
我们学到了很多
今天关于彼此。
You know, I thought I'd go crazy
你知道吗，我以为我会发疯
without all my friends
and acquaintances around
没有我所有的朋友
以及周围的熟人
but it looks like  you  were
all I needed to stay sane.
但看起来你是
我需要保持理智的一切。
What? A puppet
of my old best friend?
什么？一个木偶
我最好的老朋友？
Made entirely
of Krabby Patty meat?
完全制作
蟹肉饼肉？
Oh, Boatie, you are a card.
哦，博蒂，你是一张卡片。
Sorry I'm late, Patrick.
抱歉我迟到了，帕特里克。
Boatie was
telling me a joke.
博蒂是
给我讲个笑话。
SpongeBob: You're awfully
chummy with that guy
海绵宝宝：你太糟糕了
和那个家伙交好
for someone who has
it out for you.
对于有的人
为你准备好了。
Who, Boatie?
谁，博蒂？
No, no, he's...
不不不，他是……
Really?
真的吗？
I can't talk now.
我现在不能说话。
He's watching us.
他在看着我们。
Wait, Patrick, don't go.
等等，帕特里克，别走。
Huh?
啊？
Nothing, Boatie.
没什么，博蒂。
I'm just going to bed.
我要去睡觉了。
French man: Three days later.
法国人：三天后。
"Dear diary, not sure if
I can trust any vehicle.
“亲爱的日记，不知道是否
我可以信任任何车辆。
Run for it as soon
as the coast is clear."
尽快跑去吧
因为海岸畅通无阻。”
Ah, ah!
啊啊啊！
Ah, ah, ahh...
啊啊啊啊……
Huh?
啊？
Sheesh,
calm down, boy.
谢什，
冷静点，男孩。
You're all
still alive?
你们都是
还活着吗？
But where did you go?
但你去哪儿了？
It was national
"No SpongeBob Day".
原来是全国性的
“没有海绵宝宝日”。
National "No SpongeBob Day"?
全国“无海绵宝宝日”？
Yeah, a whole day dedicated
是的，一整天的奉献
to getting away from you.
远离你。
A day? But you guys have
been away for weeks.
一天？但你们有
已经离开好几个星期了。
Uh...  .
呃....
Yeah, well, we kind of
milked it a little.
是的，好吧，我们有点
挤一点奶。
You too, Patrick?
你也是吗，帕特里克？
: Yeah.
： 是的。
Everybody needs at least
one day away from...
每个人至少需要
有一天，远离...
Well,
glad you had fun.
嗯，
很高兴你玩得开心。
Aw, cheer up, boy.
噢，振作起来，男孩。
It's a whole day
inspired by you.
已经是一整天了
受到你的启发。
Really?
真的吗？
Of course.
当然。
First we build
a giant wooden effigy of you.
首先我们构建
你的巨型木制雕像。
Then we burn it to the ground.
然后我们把它烧毁。
Krabs: Whoo-hoo.
螃蟹：呼呼。
Krabs: Burn baby, whoo.
螃蟹：烧伤宝贝，呼。
Krabs: And dance on the ashes
like there was no tomorrow.
螃蟹：在灰烬上跳舞
就像没有明天一样。
Wow.
哇。
A whole day dedicated to me.
一整天都奉献给我。
Big deal.
有什么大不了的。
Wait'll you see
"No Patrick Day".
等等你会看到
“没有帕特里克节”。
Come on, everyone,
let's go.
来吧，大家，
我们走吧。
Ooh.
哦。
Where did everybody go?
大家都去哪儿了？
Hello?
你好？
: Hello?
： 你好？